[{"question_type": "single", "question": "A Python object is most similar to a ____.", "answers": ["noun"], "incorrect": ["verb", "adjective", "union"], "category": "objects", "difficulty": 0, "uuid": "e85975b7-44e1-4b68-96f1-b98f0e24a7f0"}, {"question_type": "multiple", "question": "Select the built-in object types:", "answers": ["int", "str", "list", "set"], "incorrect": ["vec", "vector", "double"], "category": "objects", "difficulty": 1, "uuid": "cd9b537d-fe0a-4831-8202-dfcf55df1dcc"}, {"question_type": "numerical", "question": "What is the value of c: <code><br>a = 5<br>b = 2<br>c = a**b</code>", "answers": [25], "incorrect": [], "category": "operators", "difficulty": 2, "uuid": "c9cffe01-a7f5-41b7-8279-6d0359fa1d4b"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "The ____ object is not mutable.", "answers": ["tuple"], "incorrect": ["list", "set", "dict"], "category": "objects", "difficulty": 1, "uuid": "94dcf13d-a089-480c-a1f3-6e2fc7bab6db"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "<code>[1, 2, 3]</code> is a ____", "answers": ["list"], "incorrect": ["set", "dict", "vec", "int"], "category": "objects", "difficulty": 1, "uuid": "1c4fa613-9d6d-47f9-868f-8d7ffbcdfc11"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "<code>{'a', 'b', 'c', 'd'}</code> is a ____", "answers": ["set"], "incorrect": ["list", "dict", "vec", "str"], "category": "objects", "difficulty": 1, "uuid": "35828ecf-8f17-44f7-8e35-63a4c846774d"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "<code>{'a': 1, 'b': 1, 'c': 2, 'd': 5}</code> is a ____", "answers": ["dict"], "incorrect": ["list", "hash", "vec", "keyval"], "category": "objects", "difficulty": 1, "uuid": "ada82b0d-debb-4b5e-8b58-469595ecfe79"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "____ is not a Python keyword.", "answers": ["foreach"], "incorrect": ["in", "and", "type", "None"], "category": "misc", "difficulty": 2, "uuid": "9f9be79d-e108-4174-9ce6-fe37efebcad8"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "Dictionary keys must be ____", "answers": ["immutable"], "incorrect": ["integers", "builtins", "incrementing"], "category": "objects", "difficulty": 5, "uuid": "1a0529eb-6d4c-4108-bb69-fc820046f679"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "To define a new object class, Python uses the ____ keyword.", "answers": ["class"], "incorrect": ["def", "cls", "fn", "object"], "category": "objects", "difficulty": 1, "uuid": "0599f10e-2699-4d52-8287-3912ebec5f68"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "Under the covers, the len funcion calls ____.", "answers": ["__len__"], "incorrect": ["__size__", "__shape__", "__length", "index[-1]"], "category": "objects", "difficulty": 5, "uuid": "b420f8ec-2645-42ef-b1d0-4506333cc34b"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "Under the covers, the len funcion calls ____.", "answers": ["__len__"], "incorrect": ["__size__", "__shape__", "__length", "index[-1]"], "category": "objects", "difficulty": 5, "uuid": "10799038-901f-45fe-906b-b37187956b16"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "To handle errors, Python uses _____", "answers": ["try/except"], "incorrect": ["try/catch", "if/else", "do/except", "do/catch"], "category": "objects", "difficulty": 4, "uuid": "b82e87f8-3a0b-4c7d-9480-a08f82029190"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "This object evaluates as 'True'", "answers": ["-1"], "incorrect": ["None", "list()", "set()"], "category": "objects", "difficulty": 3, "uuid": "c18225f3-ef67-4027-94a7-d10a03ce9de6"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "The default return type of a python function is ____.", "answers": ["None"], "incorrect": ["Nothing, there is no default.", "null", "NaN", "0"], "category": "functions", "difficulty": 4, "uuid": "2ae52637-653b-4a15-813c-c749aa7ad1b2"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "Two types of function inputs are positional arguments and ____ arguments.", "answers": ["keyword"], "incorrect": ["conditional", "parametric", "variable"], "category": "functions", "difficulty": 5, "uuid": "e8f1c397-6e25-46ba-bd22-d3f925ca852a"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "Keyword arguments are ____", "answers": ["optional"], "incorrect": ["not supported in python", "invalid", "deprecated", "default"], "category": "functions", "difficulty": 6, "uuid": "c7d874f7-19dd-4ade-a008-4f2e394b49e0"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "The built-in function equivalent of '*' is found in the ____ library.", "answers": ["operator"], "incorrect": ["functools", "collections", "numpy", "matlab", "mathematics"], "category": "operators", "difficulty": 6, "uuid": "5f2a433b-4d4f-43f1-a793-1bc93bfbedb1"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "Trying to access a non-existent key in a dictionary throws a ____.", "answers": ["KeyError"], "incorrect": ["ValueError", "TypeError", "RuntimeException", "DictError"], "category": "misc", "difficulty": 3, "uuid": "caba10e8-6111-41ed-bc9b-ae80602163e8"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "One way to access an object's members is ____.", "answers": ["getattr()"], "incorrect": ["get()", "<object>::<member>", "getmember()", "<object>-><member>"], "category": "objects", "difficulty": 4, "uuid": "f3cf7f27-d018-464d-a33d-2eb0ba704791"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "Checking an objects type/inheritence can be done with ____.", "answers": ["isinstance()"], "incorrect": ["hasattr()", "istype()", "parent()", "child()"], "category": "objects", "difficulty": 3, "uuid": "6802fa48-482b-4be8-a8e5-2823375981c9"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "The ____ keyword is used to create anonymous functions.", "answers": ["lambda"], "incorrect": ["anon", "def", "class", "omega", "alpha"], "category": "functions", "difficulty": 5, "uuid": "8c070d84-1ccc-497c-88b5-462be16f4d64"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "Trying to access a non-existent key in a dictionary throws a ____.", "answers": ["KeyError"], "incorrect": ["ValueError", "TypeError", "RuntimeException", "DictError"], "category": "objects", "difficulty": 3, "uuid": "2c3775c3-82f4-42b0-83c8-ff9c7792a23d"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "The ____ keyword skips to the next iteration of a loop.", "answers": ["continue"], "incorrect": ["next", "skip", "pass"], "category": "misc", "difficulty": 3, "uuid": "0b40a302-f360-4398-b26e-a6debf6a3df5"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "Most collections can be sorted using ____", "answers": ["sorted"], "incorrect": ["sort", "order", "ascending"], "category": "misc", "difficulty": 3, "uuid": "5a538030-befe-4445-8766-36aed1de8d83"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "Iterating over two collections simultaneously can be done with ____.", "answers": ["zip"], "incorrect": ["concat", "simul", "while", "together"], "category": "misc", "difficulty": 3, "uuid": "f7521c1e-a593-47e2-8dfc-10b7fe5373c6"}, {"question_type": "single", "question": "The resulting object type of <code>5 * 8.0</code> is ____.", "answers": ["float"], "incorrect": ["int", "TypeError", "bigint", "u8"], "category": "operators", "difficulty": 3, "uuid": "3b01b886-4bbd-408d-974c-f43119a07871"}]